let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "A collection of records is_______?",
    answer: "File",
    options: ["Function", "File", "File Upload", "Date"]
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Brushing teeth is twice a day?",
    answer: "True",
    options: ["True", "False", "Sometimes", "everytime"]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "All are input device except?",
    answer: "Monitor",
    options: ["Mouse", "Monitor", "Light Pen", "Keyboard"]
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "A place where buyers and sellers meet is called?",
    answer: "Market",
    options: ["Shop", "Office", "Market", "Road"]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The person who produce drug is_______",
    answer: "Pharmacist",
    options: ["Pharmacy", "Pharmacism", "Parmacist", "Pharmacist"]
  },

  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "A place where two rivers meet is called_____?",
    answer: "Confluence",
    options: ["Valley", "Lake", "Confeluence", "Confluence"]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "What does CDN stand for?",
    answer: "Content Delivery Network",
    options: [
      "Content Delivery Network",
      "Create Delivery Network",
      "Cascading Development Network",
      "Content Delivery Natation"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "What does SEO stand for?",
    answer: "Search Engine Optimization",
    options: [
      "Stylish Engine Object",
      "Search Engine Optimization",
      "Statement Engine Optimization",
      "Searh Environment Object"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What does CSS stands for?",
    answer: "Cascading Style Sheet",
    options: [
      "Cascading Styling Sheet",
      "Cascade Style Sheet",
      "Cascadent Style Sheet",
      "Cascading Style Sheet"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What is the largest search engine?",
    answer: "Google",
    options: ["Yahoo", "Bing", "Facebook", "Google"]
  },

  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "What language is a markup language?",
    answer: "HTML",
    options: ["JAVA", "PYTHON", "GOLANG", "HTML"]
  },

  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "What does INEC stands for?",
    answer: "Independent National Electoral Commission",
    options: [
      "Independent Nigeria Electoral Commission",
      "International National Electoral Commission",
      "Independent National Election Commission",
      "Independent National Electoral Commission"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "First secondary school in Nigeria is_________?",
    answer: "CMS Grammar School",
    options: [
      "CMS Grammar School",
      "Solid Rock Academy",
      "Remo Secondary School",
      "Sagamu High School"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "What does ITF stand for?",
    answer: "Industrial Training Fund",
    options: [
      "Independent Training Fund",
      "Industrial Teaching Foundation",
      "Industrial Training Fund",
      "Institute Teaching Fund"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "What does WHO stand for?",
    answer: "World Health Organization",
    options: [
      "World Health Organization",
      "World Health Origination",
      "World Heart Organization",
      "Word Health Organization"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Which country host FIFA 2022 CUP?",
    answer: "Qatar",
    options: ["Nigeria", "Japan", "Ghana", "Qatar"]
  },

  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "What does NECO stands for?",
    answer: "National Examination Council",
    options: [
      "Nigeria Examination Concil",
      "NAtional Exercise Country",
      "National Examination Council",
      "National Experiment Council"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "A person that attends to guest in an office is_____?",
    answer: "Receptionist",
    options: ["Manager", "Director", "Receptionist", "Reception"]
  },

  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "Who created the Internet?",
    answer: "Tim Berners Lee",
    options: ["Bill Gates", "Prof. Ahmed Musa", "Jeff Bezos", "Tim Berners Lee"]
  },

  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "A thought or suggestion is known as _______?",
    answer: "Idea",
    options: ["Thinking", "Idea", "Reason", "No idea"]
  },

  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "Who is the owner of facebook?",
    answer: "Mark Zuckerberg",
    options: ["Bill Gates", "Elon Musk", "Mark Zuckerberg", "Jeff Bezos"]
  },

  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "Facebook was change from its former name to______?",
    answer: "Meta",
    options: ["Whatsapp", "Meta", "TweetMe", "Metar"]
  },

  {
    numb: 23,
    question: "What does ND stands for?",
    answer: "National Diploma",
    options: [
      "Nigeria Directorate",
      "National Diplomatic",
      "New Direction",
      "National Diploma"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 24,
    question: "What does PGD stands for?",
    answer: "Post Graduate Diploma",
    options: [
      "Pre Graduate Diplom",
      "Post Graduate Diplomee",
      "Post Graduate Diploma",
      "Per Grade Direction"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "What does CLI stands for?",
    answer: "Command LIne Interface",
    options: [
      "Command Line Info",
      "Center Line Info",
      "Command LIne Interface",
      "Correct Linear Interface"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 26,
    question: "Best linux for pentesting is ____?",
    answer: "Kali",
    options: ["Windows", "Ubuntu", "Kalii", "Kali"]
  },

  {
    numb: 27,
    question: "Step by step procedure of solving task is ____?",
    answer: "Algorithm",
    options: ["Alghorithm", "Algorithm", "Algorithn", "Arlgorithm"]
  },

  {
    numb: 28,
    question: "All are examples of output device except_____?",
    answer: "Mouse",
    options: ["Monitor", "Speaker", "Printer", "Mouse"]
  },

  {
    numb: 29,
    question: "None is vector quantites except ____?",
    answer: "Distance",
    options: ["Height", "Weight", "Distance", "Width"]
  },

  {
    numb: 30,
    question: "All are figure of speech except____?",
    answer: "Preposition",
    options: ["Simile", "Preposition", "Metaphor", "Hyperbole"]
  }
];
